《迷失》前情提要
Previously on "lost"...
-那是Benjamin Linus吗  -我们要你救他
- Is that Benjamin Linus? - We need you to save his life.
如果我把他带走  他就会改头换面
If I take him, he's not ever gonna be the same again.
永远成为我们的一员
He will always be one of us.
赶紧给我滚出来  不然我毙了你女儿
Get your ass out here right now, or I'm gonna kill your daughter.
她是我从一个疯女人那里偷来的
I stole her as a baby from an insane woman.
我根本不在乎她  所以如果你想杀她
She means nothing to me. so if you want to kill her,
尽管动手吧
Go ahead and do it...
这个人很危险
This guy is dangerous.
Sun  我来这里所乘的船上全是突击队
Sun, that boat I came here on was filled with commandos
他们的唯一使命就是抓到他
Whose only mission was to get him.
看看后来怎么了
And how'd that work out for everyone?
-你认识他吗  -认识
- You know him? - Yeah.
他就是杀我的凶手
He's the man who killed me.
-你都做了什么  Richard  -镇定
- What have you done, Richard? - Calm down
-镇定  这件事与你无关  -那就是真的
- Calm down. this has nothing to do with you. - So it's true?
你真的把他们的成员带到我们神殿
You actually brought one of them to our temple?
他只是个孩子  而且生命垂危
He's just a boy, and he was dying.
那就顺其自然
Then you should've let him die.
Jacob想让我救他
Jacob wanted it done.
这座岛的选择不容抗辩
The island chooses is the island's chooses.
你也知道
You know that.
对  对  那是当然
Yes. yes, of course.
他叫什么名字
What's his name?
你好  Benjamin
Hello, Benjamin.
发生了什么事
What happened?
你受伤了
You were injured.
怎么会
How?
你不记得了吗
You don't remember?
我现在哪里
Where am i?
你和朋友们在一起
You're among friends.
我们会照顾你
We're going to take care of you.
我爸呢  他在吗
My dad...is he here?
你很快就能回到他身边
You'll be back to him soon enough.
不  不  我不想回去
No. no, I don't want to go back.
好  放松  放松
Okay, easy. easy. oh!
我不想回去
I don't want to go back.
我想留下
I wanna stay.
我想加入你们
I wanna be one of you.
你和他们同住在一起
Just because you're living with them
不代表你就不能成为我们一员
Doesn't mean you can't be one of us.
你本该已经死了  Benjamin
You should be dead, Benjamin.
可这座岛
But this island...
救了你的命
It saved your life.
你是谁
Who are you?
我叫Charles
I'm Charles.
Charles Widmore
Charles widmore.
Ben
Ben.
你好  Ben
Hello, Ben.
欢迎回到人间
Welcome back to the land of the living.
天呐
My god.
你还活着
You're alive.
没错
Yes, I am.
我就知道
I knew it.
我就知道会这样
I knew that this would happen.
那你为什么见到我还那么惊讶
Then why are you so surprised to see me?
John  因为相信是一回事
Because it's one thing to believe it, John.
亲眼验证又是另一回事
It's another thing to see it.
那你为什么还想方设法逃到主岛上
Then why were you trying to run away to the main island?
John  我打破了规则
I broke the rules,John.
回到了岛上
I came back to the island.
我当时想为我的所作所为负责
I was going to answer for what I'd done.
我当时正要回去
I was going back...
接收审判
To be judged.
审判
Judged?
谁审判
By whom?
John
Well, j-john,
它还没有名字
We don't even have a word for it,
可我相信  你会叫它"怪物"
But I believe you call it the monster.
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多字幕 美剧 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译：  非燕  发疯  牛牛  zhjing
校对：  非燕  大菜  许愿　 时间轴： after
■
后期：  冰蚕　　 剧集总监： 非燕
早啊
Morning.
你好
Hello.
箱子里装的什么
What's in the crate?
只是些行动必备的行装
Just some stuff we need to get moved.
要帮忙吗
Need a hand?
谢谢  不用了
Oh, thanks. we got it.
好  万事顺意
Okay. have a great day.
朋友  你感觉怎样
How you feeling, my friend?
就像有人用桨敲了我  可我还活着
Like someone hit me with an oar, but I'll live.
-你觉得他这人怎样  -不好说
- What do you make of him? - I'm not sure.
他对你说了什么
What has he told you?
你失去直觉时  他一直照看着你
When you were out cold, he was watching over you.
他说你杀了他
And he said you killed him.
我杀了他
I killed him?
真的吗  可我看他现在好好的
Really? 'cause he looks fine to me.
我不记得他是飞机上的乘客
You know, I don't really remember him from the plane.
-你记得他吗  -不  我不记得了
- Do you? - No, I don't.
要是
What if...
我们坠机前  他就已经在这里了呢
He was already here, before we crashed?
如果他认为我杀了他  那他就是疯子
If he thinks I killed him, then he's insane.
我们可能在和精神错乱的人打交道
We may be dealing with a man who's dangerously deranged.
那问题就是  我们该怎样应付呢
Then the question is, what are we gonna do about it?
别担心  朋友
Don't worry, my friend.
我支持你
I have your back.
我叫Caesar
Caesar.
很高兴认识你  Ceasar  我叫Ben
Pleasure to meet you, Caesar. I'm Ben.
要我动手吗
You want me to do it?
只要你开口  我就动手  Ben
I can do it if you want me to, ben.
闭嘴
Shut up!
乖乖呆在这里  Ethan
And stay here, Ethan.
别  别这样
Don't! don't do it.
你就是让我们受感染的人  对吗
You're the one who infected us, aren't you?!
不  （法语）
不
No! shh.
-别带走我孩子（法语）  -没事的  没事的
- Donnez... -It's okay. it's okay, baby.
求你了  别带走我的Alex
Please, don't take my Alex!
还想让你孩子活命吗
Do you want your baby to live?
为什么要带走她
Why are you taking her?!
感谢上苍你还活着吧
Be grateful you're still alive.
你给我听着
Now you listen to me.
如果你跟踪我  或者来找我
If you try to follow me or if you ever come looking for me,
我就杀了你
I'll kill you.
如果你还想保住你孩子的命
And if you want your child to live,
只要你听到低声细语  就往另一边跑
Every time you hear whispers, you run the other way.
那是什么
What's that?
一些让人伤感的东西
Just something sentimental.
这就是你的旧办公室
So this is your old office, huh?
我从没想过你会在坐在办公桌前
I never pictured you leading your people
领导你的人
From behind a desk.
这有点像
It seems a little...
公司
Corporate.
-你想要什么吗  John  -Ben  我希望
- Was there something that you needed, John? - Well, Ben, I was hoping
能聊聊你我都心知肚明  却闭口不谈的事
That you and I could talk about the elephant in the room.
我想你指的是我杀你那件事吧
I assume you're referring to the fact that I killed you.
对
Yeah.
那是让你回到岛上的唯一办法
It was the only way to get you back to the island,
还有那些离开的人
Along with as many of those who left as possible.
你应该记得  所以你才率先离开
You do remember, John...that's why you left in the first place,
去说服他们回来
To convince 'em to come back?
可事与愿违
But you failed.
唯一能把他们聚到一起的方法
And the only way to bring them together
就是你死  你自己也明白这点
Was by your death, and you understood that.
这就是当你自杀时我要阻止的原因
It's why you were about to kill yourself when i stopped you.
如果真的要我死  Ben  你为什么阻止我
If all i had to do was die, Ben, then why did you stop me?
因为你拥有一些重要的信息
You had critical information that would've died with you.
一旦你给了我
And once you'd given it to me...
我当时没有时间
Well, i just didn't have time
去劝你再次把你自己吊死
To talk you back into hanging yourself.
所以我走了捷径
So i took a shortcut.
你看现在的你  John  我当时是对的
And look at you, John. i was right.
你回来了  还有其他的人
You're here. you're back. so are the rest of them.
虽然不知道在哪里  但是也一起回来了
I don't know where yet exactly, but they came. it worked.
这才是我当时杀你的原因
And that's why i did it,
因只有这样才能符合这座岛的利益
Because it was in the best interests of the island.
我一直等你道歉呢
I was just hoping for an apology.
我决定助你一臂之力  Ben
I've decided to help you, Ben.
帮助我做什么
Help me do what?
帮助你完成你未完成的事
Do what you say you are on your way to do.
接收审判
Be judged.
后果会不堪设想  John
That's not something you want to see, John.
如果你所做的一切
If everything you've done
都是为了这座岛的利益
Has been in the best interests of the island...
那么我保证那怪物会理解的
Then i'm sure the monster will understand.
走吧
Let's go.
-你们在做什么  -我们要用这条船
- What are you doing? - We're taking a boat.
去哪里
Where?
去对面的主岛
Over to the main island.
我可不那么想  朋友
I don't think so, my friend.
这些是你的船吗
Are these your boats?
难道是你的吗
Are they yours?
你叫Caesar  是吗
Caesar, right?
我记得这些船是在这里被发现的
I was under the impression these were found here
所以我想借一条船
So i'm just gonna borrow one.
我很愿意把剩下的船留给你们
I'm happy to leave the other boat for you
-你们也可以跟着我们  -"我们"
- In case you want to follow us.   - "us"?
你要和他一起吗
Are you going with him?
他都没有给我选择的余地
He didn't really give me a choice.
不好意思  但是这里我说的算
I'm sorry, but i'm calling the shots here
你不能拿走任何东西
And i say you are not taking anything.
你所需要做得就是坐下来
What you are going to do is to sit down
告诉我们你怎么知道的那么多
And tell us how you know so much
关于这座岛的事情
about this island you mean it.my friend
你习惯把别人称做"朋友"
You're in the habit of calling people "friend,"
但我不认为你当真的
But i don't think you mean it.
-离船远一点  -不
-Step away from the boat.  -no. i'm
我绝不会离开这条船
not gonna step awe the boats
我要把它带走  希望你能同意  朋友
I'm gonna take it, and you're gonna let me, my friend.
你什么都别想拿走
You're not taking anything.
你在找这个吗
you looking for this?
先生们  我把这条船带走了
This gentleman and i are taking a boat.
还有谁有异议吗
Does anyone else have a problem with that?
算是我的道歉吧
Consider that my apology.
家  温馨的家
Home, sweet home.
看来我们不是最早
Looks like we're not the first
决定来这里的人
ones who decided to tie up here
一定是Sun和Lapidus
That would be Sun and Lapidus.
我告诉他们船的位置
I showed 'em where the boats were,
Sun用船桨把我打晕  表达对我的感激之情
And Sun thanked me by smashing me on the head with a paddle.
她是那个把你手弄伤的人
Oh. is she the one that hurt your arm?
我注意到  你一路上都很小心  不碰上手臂
I noticed you were favoring it on the way over.
不是
No.
是其他人把我的手弄伤了
Someone else hurt my arm.
不管到哪里你都不断的结交朋友  是把
You just make friends everywhere you go, don't ya?
有时候我发现朋友可以
Well, i've found sometimes that friends can be
比敌人还要危险  John
Significantly more dangerous than enemies, John.
这就是为什么你要杀那个手无寸铁的人吗
Is that why you shot an unarmed man in the chest?
那个人手无寸铁是因为我偷了他的枪
The man was unarmed because i'd stolen his gun...
他打算用那枪杀了你
The gun he was going to use to kill you.
我再死一次也不要紧  是把
No sense in me dying twice, right?
不客气
You're welcome.
我们现在去你的老房子是吧
We're going to your old house, aren't we?
是的
Yes.
唯一我可以召唤它的地方
It's the only place i can summon it...
那个"怪物"
The "monster."
等它来了  它要不宽恕我
Once it arrives, i'll either be forgiven...
要不处置我
Or i won't.
我感觉你在说谎
I think you're lying.
说什么谎
Lying about what?
你想因为离开岛而接收审判
That you want to be judged for leaving the island
现在回来是因为你坏了规矩
And coming back because it's against the rules.
我不觉得你关心规矩
I don't think you care about rules.
那我因为什么要接受审判  John
Then what do i want to be judged for, John?
因为你杀了你的女儿
For killing your daughter.
你下手了吗
Did you do it?
事情...
We had a...
有些复杂
Complication.
那是一个婴儿吗
I'm sorry. is that a... baby?
你的命令是去杀了那女的
Your orders were to exterminate that woman.
为什么  Charles  她没有威胁到我们  她疯了
Why? she's no threat to us. she's insane, Charles.
而且你没有告诉我她有个小孩
Besides, you didn't tell me she had a child.
那你觉得我该怎么做
What was it i was supposed to do?
杀了它
Kill it.
这不是动物  而是个婴儿
It's not an "it." this is a child.
你会发现这有些难以理解  Benjamin
You might find this difficult to understand, Benjamin...
我做的每一个决定都是
Every decision i've made has been about
为了保护这座岛
Protecting this island.
Jacob真的想杀了这个婴儿吗
Is killing this baby what Jacob wants?
给你
Then here she is.
你来动手
You do it.
搬来这里是谁的主意
So whose idea was it to move into these houses?
你说什么
Excuse me?
你们原来都住在丛林里
Well, your people were living in the jungle.
然后你把达摩组织的人都杀了
And then after you murdered the Dharma folk,
你们搬到了这里
You relocated here.
我想知道这是不是你的主意
I just wondered if it was your idea.
你不赞成这样吗  John
Do you disapprove, John?
好像并不是这个岛的意思
It just doesn't seem like something the island would want.
你不知道这个岛的初衷是什么
You don't have the first idea what this island wants.
你确定吗
Are you sure about that?
那是你的房子吗
That was your house, wasn't it?
是的  那个是Alex的房间
Yes, and that's Alex's room.
我建议你最好进去看看
Well, i suppose you better go over there and check it out.
Sun
Sun?
你在这里做什么
What are you doing here?
这以前是我的房子  我看到灯亮着
This used to be my house. i saw a light turned on.
你们两个在这里做什么
What are the two of you doing in here?
-这个是1977年照的  -你想说...
- That was taken in 1977.  - Are you trying to tell me
你的朋友加入了达摩组织
That your friends were in the Dharma initiative?
你不知道这个吗
You don't know about this?
当然不知道
Of course not.
你从哪里拿个照片  谁给你的
Where did you get this? who gave this to you?
我们在外面遇到个老疯子
We met some crazy old man outside.
他说他的名字叫Christian
He said his name was Christian.
-他告诉我们来这里等着  -等什么
- He told us to come in here and wait. - Wait for what?
他说如果我还想见到我的丈夫的话
He said if i ever wanted to see my husband again,
我就需要等John Locke
I had to wait here for John locke.
但是一想到他已经死了  我们就伤心欲绝
But considering he's dead, we ain't holding our breath.
你应该往窗外看看
Well, you might want to look outside.
你所说的都
What you're saying, it's...
不可能
Impossible.
但是我确实在这
But here I am.
我不知道怎么来的  也不知道为什么
I don't know how, I don't know why,
但是我知道这肯定有原因
But I'm sure there's a very good reason for it.
既然那个死人说有原因
As long as the dead guy says there's a reason,
我想所有的事肯定会有合理解释的
Well, then I guess everything's gonna be just peachy.
大家伙... 他们都是30年前的人
And forget about the fact that the rest of your people Are supposedly 30 years ago...
现在唯一能帮我们的
Now the only ones who are here to help us
是一个杀手和一个不记得
Are a murderer and a guy who can't seem to remember
怎么从棺材中爬出来的人
How the hell he got out of a coffin.
Sun  回到计划上来吧
Sun, please, let's just go back to the plane,
我试试能不能修好收音机   或许能有帮助
See if I can fix the radio, and maybe we can get some help.
如果你和他走
If you leave with him,
就会永远也找不到你丈夫了
you'll never find your husband again.
我是唯一能帮你的人
I'm all the help you need.
你是说你知道怎么找到他们
Are you saying you know how to find them?
怎么找到找到Jin
How to find Jin?
我有个主意
I have some ideas.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry to say,
看来我们不能一起离开了
But I'm leaving with or without you.
只要有一线希望能找到我的丈夫
If there's any chance of finding my husband,
我就会留下来
Then I have to stay.
好吧
All right.
上天保佑  小心些
For god sake, watch your back.
好了
All right.
我们怎么能找到Jin
How do we find Jin?
Ben要先做些事  是吧  Ben
Ben has something to do first. isn't that right, Ben?
是的John  没错
Yes, John. That's right.
那我们就开始吧
Better get to it then.
我要出去了
I'll be outside.
再来  爸爸
Again, daddy! again!
好的 Alex
Okay. okay. wow, Alex!
再高些  我们就要飞上天了
Any higher, and you're gonna fly right off the island.
潜艇要出发了
The sub's about to leave.
再高些  爸爸
Higher, daddy! higher!
好的
All right.
你不一定非要送他  Ben
You don't have to see him off, Ben.
不  Richard   我要送他
Yes, Richard, I do.
高些  再高些  爸爸
Higher! higher, daddy!
Charles
Charles!
我是来说再见的
I came to say good-bye.
不  你是在幸灾乐祸
No, you didn't. you came to gloat.
不  我也不想这样
No, don't act as if I wanted this.
是你自食其果
You brought this on yourself.
你确定要这么做吗  Benjamin
Are you quite certain you want to do this, benjamin?
你经常离开小岛  你的女儿...
You left the island regularly. you had a daughter
和外面的人相好  Charles
With an outsider. you broke the rules, charles.
你凭什么认为你可以得到我的东西
And what makes you think you deserve to take what's mine?
因为我不想那么自私
Because I won't be selfish.
因为我将不惜一切保护这个小岛
Because I'll sacrifice anything to protect this island.
你才不会不惜一切  Alex
You wouldn't sacrifice alex.
你想让她死  Charles
You're the one who wanted her dead, charles,
而不是小岛
Not the island.
希望你是对的  Benjamin
I hope you're right, benjamin,
因为如果你错了
Because if you aren't,
那就是这个小岛想让她死
And it is the island that wants her dead,
她就死定了
She'll be dead.
有一天  你会跟我一样站在这
And one day, you'll be standing where I'm standing now.
被驱逐出去
You'll be the one being banished,
你会意识到
And then you'll finally realize
你根本无法改变必然发生的事
That you cannot fight the inevitable.
走着瞧  伙计
I'll be seeing you, boy.
John去哪了
Where did john go?
他说要处理些事
He said he had something to do.
他去干吗了
Did he say what it was?
我没问
No, I didn't ask.
Jack肯定在撒谎
Jack must have lied.
- 什么  - Locke真的死了吗
Excuse me? about locke being dead?
我不知道他为什么撒谎  不过这是唯一的解释
I don't know why he would, but that's the only explanation.
Jack没有撒谎  John确实死了
Jack didn't lie. john was dead.
不意味着他伪装了自己的死亡
Doesn't mean that he couldn't have faked his dea...
相信我  他真的死了
Trust me. I'm sure.
所以你知道如果我们回去的话
So you knew this would happen to locke
这一切也会发生在Locke身上
If we brought him back here?
Sun  我不知道会发生这些
Sun, I had no idea it would happen.
我看到了小岛上发生的奇事
I've seen this island do miraculous things.
我看到它治愈了疾病
I've seen it heal the sick,
但都不像这件事
But never once has it done anything like this.
死了就死了
Dead is dead.
死了就不能复生了
You don't get to come back from that,
在这儿也不行
Not even here.
当John Locke出现在小岛上
So the fact that john locke is walking around this island...
我被吓的魂飞魄散
Scares the living hell out of me.
你该进去了
You may want to go inside.
为什么
Why?
因为树丛里有我不能控制的东西
Because what's about to come out of that jungle is something I can't control.
怎么样了
Any luck?
还没出现
It hasn't shown up yet.
上次我们没等这么久
Last time we didn't have to wait this long.
这不是火车  John  不是按时刻表来的
It's not a train, john. it doesn't run on a schedule.
好吧  如果它不出现  那...
Well, if it's not gonna come to us, then...
我想我们就只能自己找它了
I suppose we'll have to go to it.
它不是这么工作的  我只知道怎么召唤它
It doesn't work that way. I only know how to summon it.
我并不知道它究竟在哪
I don't know where it actually is.
我知道
I do.
我也觉得很不可思议
It's weird for me, too.
什么
Excuse me?
我知道这奇怪...
I realize how strange this all is...
我出现在这
Me, here.
但是我像你保证  Sun
But I assure you, sun,
我跟过去的我是同一个人
I'm the same man I've always been.
准备好了吗
Are you ready?
带路吧
Lead the way.
喂
Hello?
Charles  我是Benjanmin
Charles? it's Benjamin.
你怎么知道这个号码的
How did you get this number?
这并不重要  重要的是
Doesn't matter. what matters is
我今天要返回小岛上
I'm going back to the island today.
小岛不会让你回去的  相信我
The island won't let you come back, trust me.
我花了20年的时间企图回去
I've spent almost 20 years trying to return.
Charles  你失败了  但是我会成功的
Well, charles, where you failed, I'm going to succeed...
只要我做一件事
Just as soon as I do one thing.
什么事  Benjamin
And what's that, benjamin?
杀了你的女儿
Kill your daughter.
事实上  我现在正看着我们共同的朋友
In fact, I'm looking at "our mutual friend" right now.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
-Penny在的船的名字就是吧  -你敢
- It's the name of the boat that penny's on. - Don't you dare.
再见  Charles
Good-bye, Charles.
我能问你一个问题吗  John
May I ask you a question, John?
说
Shoot.
你怎么知道你要去哪
How is it that you know where you're going?
我是说  这具体怎么办到的
I mean, how does that work, exactly?
怎么回事
How does what work?
你知道的那些  我是说它是逐渐的
The knowing. I mean, did it come upon you gradually,
还是某一天
Or did you wake up one morning
突然出现在你的脑子里的
Suddenly understanding the mysteries of the universe?
-你不喜欢这些  对吗  -什么
- You don't like this, do you? - What?
无奈地提些
Having to ask questions
你自己都不知道答案的问题
That you don't know the answers to,
盲目地相信别人
Blindly following someone in the hopes that
希望他们能带你找到你要的东西
They'll lead you to whatever it is you're looking for.
不  John  我一点也不喜欢
No, John, I don't like it at all.
现在你知道我是怎样的人了吧
Well, now you know what it was like to be me.
我们得继续赶路
We should keep moving.
是的
Yes, we should.
我知道我们要去哪  John
I think I know where we're going now, John.
是吗
Do you?
我小时候他们带我去的地方
It's the same place they brought me as a child.
我被治愈的地方
It's where the island healed me.
但愿这次它也能大发慈悲
Let's hope it's as generous this time around.
那是什么
What is it?
神殿的围墙
It's the wall around our temple.
什么神殿
What temple?
离这一英里远
About a half mile from here.
围墙是防止你们这样的人看见神殿的
We built this wall to keep people like the two of you from ever seeing it.
我们不去你们的神殿  Ben
We're not going into your temple, Ben.
我们从下面进入
We're going under it.
你先进去
After you.
请你帮个忙  Sun
I need to ask a favor of you, Sun.
如果你能离开这个岛
If you can ever get off this island,
帮我找到Desmond Hume  告诉他我很抱歉
Find Desmond Hume for me. Tell him I said I was sorry.
为什么抱歉
Sorry for what?
他会知道的
He'll know.
你在这做什么
What are you doing here?
Desmond
Desmond!
Des
Des?!
别动
Don't move.
别说话
Not another word.
你好  Penelope
Hello, Penelope.
我是Benjamin Linus
My name is Benjamin Linus.
抱歉你卷入此事
I'm sorry that you're caught up in the middle of this thing,
-但你爸爸  -我爸爸和我
- But your father... - My father and I
没有任何关系
Have absolutely no relationship whatsoever,
-所以无论  -你爸十恶不赦
- So whatever... - Your father is a really terrible human being.
他杀了我女儿 所以我来这
He's responsible for the killing of my daughter. That's why I'm here.
妈妈
Mommy!
Charlie  回去  宝贝
Charlie, go back inside, babe.
回去  求你了
Go back inside. Please.
求你了  无论你做什么  别伤害我儿子
Please, whatever you do, don't hurt my son.
-请不要伤害我儿子  -妈妈
- Please don't hurt my son. - Mommy? Mommy?
Charlie  回去
Charlie, go inside!
Lapidus机长  Lapidus机长
Captain Lapidus! Captain Lapidus!
谢天谢地  你回来了
You're back. thank god.
他们找到了枪支
They found guns.
你说什么  谁找到了枪支
What are you talking about? who found guns?
Ilana和其他三个人
Ilana and three of the others.
他们说他们说的算
They said they were in charge now.
他们在哪
Where are they?
Ilana
Ilana!
怎么了
What's going on?
雕像的阴影里藏着什么
What lies in the shadow of the statue?
什么
What?
回答我
Answer the question!
雕像的阴影里藏着什么
What lies in the shadow of the statue?
我不知道
I have no idea what the...
把其他人找来  告诉他们时间到了
Get everyone else. tell them it's time.
把他绑起来
And tie him up.
把他带走
He's coming with us.
你说对了
You know, you were right.
关于什么
About what?
我要接受审判的原因
Why I need to be judged.
Charles Widmore的人来的时候他们给了我选择
When Charles Widmore's men came, They gave me a choice.
要么离开岛  要么对我女儿的死坐视不管
Either leave the island or let my daughter die.
我该做的只是离开房子跟他们走
All I had to do was walk out of the house and go with them.
但我没照做
But I didn't do it.
所以你是对的
So you were right.
John  是我害死了Alex
John, I did kill Alex.
现在我要为此负责
And now I have to answer for that.
很感谢你指给我方向
I appreciate you showing me the way,
我想下面该我自己走了
But I think I can take it from here.
好的
You got it.
如果我还活着  我们外面见
I'll meet you outside, if I live...
Ben
Ben!
你还好吧
Are you all right?
再好不过
Never better.
你等着  我找东西救你出来
Hang on. I'll find something to get you out of there.
John  等等
John, wait!
你没告诉我她有个孩子
You didn't tell me she had a child.
我该怎么做
What was it I was supposed to do?
-杀了它  -那不是动物  那是个孩子
- Kill it. - It's not an "it." This is a child.
再高点  再来  爸爸  再来
Higher! Again, daddy! Again!
高点  高点  爸爸
Higher! Higher, daddy!
我恨你
I hate you!
我恨死你了  你去死吧
I hate your guts! I wish you were dead.
这些人
These people...
你说他们危险
You said they're dangerous.
他们比你还危险吗
More dangerous than you?
爸爸  他们是玩真格的
Dad, they're serious.
他们杀了Karl和妈妈
They killed Karl and my mother.
求你了  爸爸
Please, dad.
救救我
Help me!
她不是我女儿
She's not my daughter.
我不在乎她
She means nothing to me.
你想杀她  那就动手吧
So if you wanna kill her, go ahead and...
爸爸
Daddy?
Alex
Alex.
爸爸
Hi, dad.
Alex
Ohh, alex.
我真的很抱歉
I'm so, so sorry.
都是我的错
It was all my fault.
我知道
I know.
听着  你这混蛋  我知道
Listen to me, you bastard! I know
你计划再杀死John
That you're already planning to kill John again,
而我要你知道  你敢碰他一下
And I want you to know that if you so much as touch him,
我会找到你  把你碎尸万段
I will hunt you down and destroy you.
你必须服从John Locke的所有命令
You will listen to every word John locke says,
你要听他指挥
And you will follow his every order.
明白吗
Do you understand?
说出来
Say it!
说你听他的
Say you'll follow him.
是的  我会  我发誓我会听他的
Yes, I will. I'll follow him. I swear.
Ben
Ben?
Ben!
Ben
Ben?
怎么了
What happened?
它让我活了下来
It let me live.